Guide to the Nicole Baran Papers SC1269
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2015-156
  - Greenbook Initiative Documents/Trainings, Series 20
    - Trainings
      - National Greenbook Domestic Violence Toolbox, 2006 (Box 18)
      - Project 2 (Box 18)
  - Nicole Baran's Presentations at National Conferences, Series 21
    These are national conferences where Baran presented; they are separated from the sample trainings in Box 23.
    - Presentation Lists (Box 28)
    - Stanford Women's Leadership Conference: How to Start a Nonprofit, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Center Referenced in Agendas (Box 28)
    - The Family Violence Prevention Fund and UCSF: National Conference on Health and Domestic Violence: Health Professional Students and Campus Activism, 2007 Mar 15 (Box 28)
    - FVPF, 2007 Mar 15-17 (Box 28)
    - CALCASA/OVW DOJ Campus Institute: Colleague to Colleague, 2007 Jun 27 (Box 28)
    - Campus Training Technical Assistance Institute with USDOJ Office on Violence Against Women in Partnership with CALCASA, 2007 Jun 27-28 (Box 28)
    - Colleague to Colleague: When Relationship Abuse Affects Our Coworkers, 2007 Jun (Box 28)
    - Workplace Training, 2007 Jun (Box 28)
    - The Greenbook Summit Planning Meeting, 2008 Nov 6-7 (Box 28)
    - Greenbook Conference, Jackson Hole, WY): National Summit on the Intersection of Domestic Violence and CM, 2009 Jun 2-4 (Box 28)
      Baran's second session was called "The Impact of Men's and Father's Rights Groups on Efforts to Address Domestic Violence and Child Welfare," presented with Jeffrey Edleson and Anne Menard, and can be found in Box 25.
    - Greenbook Summit, 2009 Jun 4 (Box 28)
      See Box 13 for more Green Book materials.
    - Greenbook Advocacy: "Practice Guidelines: Confidentiality, Information Sharing, and Supportive Advocacy," Nicole Baran and Jill Davies, 2009 Jun 4 (Box 28)
    - CPEDomestic Violence (California Partnership to End Domestic Violence) Annual Conference: Engaging the Next Generation, 2012 Sep 13-14 (Box 28)
    - Stanford Women's Leadership Conference: Speaking Truth and Moving Sand, Why it Matters, 2014 (Box 28)
      Stanford Women's Leadership Conference. Baran was asked to speak about how she got to where she is professionally. Baran spoke about Stanford controversies and burn-out. Includes full PowerPoint.
  - Mentors in Violence Prevention (MVP), Series 22
    - MVP-CLI Trainer's Guide (Box 28)
      Baran found some exercises to be victim blaming and/or problematic and edited this manual.
    - MVP Stanford Session (Box 28)
    - MVP (Box 28)
  - Sample Training File Folders, 2005, 2006, 2007, 2008, 2009, 2011; Series 23
    Many of these files were thrown out in a move; these files are what were kept and is how it was organized. There is a full training list with numbers in the front. The complete files with PowerPoints and handouts were electronic. These folders were often used by interns.
    - Sample Evaluations
      These are samples of evaluations. The rest were thrown away.
      - Participant List of All Trainings (Box 23)
      - Evals - VLSP, 2011 Nov 14 (Box 23)
      - CA Evaluations, 2011 Sep 16 (Box 23)
      - Frat. Evals, 2011 Fall (Box 23)
      - Community Center Training, 2011 May 24 (Box 23)
      - Kappa Sigma Pledge Training, 2016 May (Box 23)
      - Frat Pledge Training KA, 2012 May (Box 23)
      - Stanford HR Training, 2011 May 4 (Box 23)
    - Stanford Trainings
      - WCC Leadership Conference, 2015 Apr 5 (Box 23)
      - I-Center Training (Box 23)
      - Oh! The Places You'll Go, 2009 Sep 10 (Box 23)
      - PHE Part 2, 2009 Sep 9 (Box 23)
      - Stanford RA, 2009 Sep 3 (Box 23)
      - Bridge Training, 2009 May 26 (Box 23)
      - ASB Panel, 2009 May 21 (Box 23)
      - International Spouses, 2009 May 19 (Box 23)
      - Ralph's Alcohol Class, 2009 May 13 (Box 23)
      - PHE Presentation, 2009 Apr 23 (Box 23)
      - Frat Leadership Training, 2009 Apr 21 (Box 23)
      - MVP Fraternity Meeting, 2009 Apr 26 (Box 23)
      - FMAV Training Pt. 2, 2009 Apr 28 (Box 23)
      - Her Story, 2009 Aor 20 (Box 23)
      - Frat Pledge Workshop, 2009 Spring-Fall (Box 23)
      - Stanford CA Training, 2009 Feb 18 (Box 23)
      - Community Police Academy, 2009 Feb 5 (Box 23)
      - Sexual Harassment Advisors, 2008 Nov 14 (Box 23)
      - CAPS Fellows, 2008 Dec 5 (Box 23)
      - Oh The Places You'll Go, 2008 Sep 11 (Box 23)
      - Stanford RA, 2008 Sep 4 (Box 23)
      - I-Center /Community Center, 2007 Dec 7 (Box 23)
      - Stanford CA, 2007 Sep14 (Box 23)
      - Stanford RA, 2007 Sep 4 (Box 23)
      - Stanford Domestic Violence Pro-Bono Clinic, 2007 Sep 13 (Box 23)
      - PHE, 2007 Apr 24 (Box 23)
      - Frat Talk (Box 23)
      - Disability Resource Center, 2008 May 7 (Box 23)
      - WCC Her Story, 2008 Apr 15 (Box 23)
      - Sorority Presentations, 2007 (Box 23)
      - Bridge Counseling, 2007 Oct 16 (Box 23)
      - McGann Women's Health, 2007 Oct 8 (Box 23)
      - Oh The Places You'll Go, 2007 Sep 10 (Box 23)
      - Sorority, 2007 May 30 (Box 23)
      - Theta Delt Frat, 2007 May 2 (Box 23)
      - Residence Deans, 2007 May 17 (Box 23)
      - FroSoCo, 2007 May 10 (Box 23)
      - Soto Dorm, 2007 Apr 24 (Box 23)
      - Okada Dorm, 2007 May 2 (Box 23)
      - CAPS, 2007 Mar 9 (Box 23)
      - Vaden Health Medical, 2007 Jan 11 (Box 23)
      - Know More, 2007 Feb 2 (Box 23)
      - Stanford Community Police Academy, 2007 Feb 8 (Box 23)
      - Ralph Class/Alcohol, 2007 Feb 13 (Box 23)
      - Bridge Counseling, 2006 Nov 14 (Box 23)
      - PHE Stanford, 2006 Apr 25 (Box 23)
      - SVAB, 2006 Nov 29 (Box 23)
      - Stanford RA, 2006 Sep 7 (Box 23)
      - WCC Workshop, 2006 May 30 (Box 23)
      - Starting a Nonprofit (Box 23)
      - Stanford RA Training, 2006 Feb 23 (Box 23)
      - Stanford Sorority - SYZ, 2006 Feb 26 (Box 23)
      - Stanford Med Ctr Co-Workers, 2006 Oct 13 (Box 23)
    - Non-Stanford Trainings
      - Law Enforcement, 2009 May 28 (Box 23)
      - Teen Pregnancy Coalition, 2009 Apr 6 (Box 23)
      - VLSP, 2009 Mar 17 (Box 23)
        Baran's father was the staff attorney for VLSP, SF Bar Association, and hired the Center to train staff.
      - SF DVC, 2008 Sep 15 (Box 23)
        Includes notes on why Michael Johnson is problematic.
      - SJSU MSW Training, 2007 Aug 20 (Box 23)
      - VLSP, 2007 Jun 5 (Box 23)
      - Kaiser Milpitas Pediatrics, 2007 Nov 13 (Box 23)
      - Kaiser Psychiatry, 2007 Jan 22 (Box 23)
      - SJSU MSW, 2006 Aug 30-31 (Box 23)
      - Kaiser Milpitas, 2006 Jun 5 (Box 23)
      - Kaiser Redwood, 2006 Oct 6 (Box 23)
      - Shelter Network, 2006 Aug 31 (Box 23)
      - Greenbook, 2006 Jun 16 (Box 23)
      - Notre Dame HS, 2006 Mar 16 (Box 23)
      - Mountain View HS, 2006 May 23 (Box 23)
      - Greenbook, 2006 Jun 16 (Box 23)
      - Teacher Training, 2006 Jun 19 (Box 23)
      - Achieve Kids, 2006 Jul 12 (Box 23)
      - Crisis Middle School, 2006 Mar 1 (Box 23)
      - Willard Berkeley, 2006 Sep 27 (Box 23)
      - SF Bar Association, 2006 Sep 21 (Box 23)
      - City College of San Jose, 2006 May 9 (Box 23)
      - Kaiser-Milpitas, 2006 Mar 29 (Box 23)
      - BIP Training, 2006 Mar 25 (Box 23)
      - JFK Counseling, 2005 Dec 8 (Box 23)
      - Billyde Frank, 2005 Nov 14 (Box 23)
      - SJ State Mental Health, 2005 Sep 28 (Box 23)
      - Child Abuse Prevention Council, 2005 Sep 24 (Box 23)
      - Child Abuse Prevention Center, 2005 Nov 5 (Box 23)
  - Judicial Affairs Training/Judicial Affairs Issues Complications, Series 24
    The Center, as part of the OVW grant, providing training to JA panelists. This was the first time Relationship Abuse was integrated into training. Historically, it was only sexual assault. Baran made it mandatory of 6 hours of topic training, though she wanted it to be more. It had previously only been integrated into the standard 3 hour training on JA panelist requirements.
    - Judicial Affairs Training
      - JA Pre Training Survey, 2007 (Box 12)
      - JA Pre Training Survey, 2010 (Box 12)
      - Judicial Affairs, 2011 (Box 12)
      - Judicial Panel, 2010 Summer (Box 12)
      - Relationship Abuse Sexual Violence: Judicial Panelist Training, 2010 Oct 4, 2010 Oct 11 (Box 12)
      - JA Handouts (Box 12)
      - Relationship Abuse Sexual Violence: Judicial Panelist Training, 2007 Fall (Box 12)
      - Judicial Affairs Staff, 2007 Oct 12 (Box 12)
      - [unmarked red folder] Judicial Affairs Training folder, 2007 Oct 12 (Box 12)
      - JA Training Packet (Box 12)
      - Judicial Affairs, 2009 Feb 3 (Box 12)
      - JA Prep (Box 12)
      - Judicial Affairs Handouts (Box 12)
      - Case Studies (Box 12)
      - Judicial Panel, 2007 Oct 30, 2007 Oct 25, 2007 Nov 3 (Box 12)
      - Judicial Affairs, 2007 Jan 11, 2007 Jan 16 (Box 12)
      - YWCA JA Sexual Assault Training (Box 12)
    - Judicial Affairs Issues/Complications
      - Judicial Affairs Numbers (Box 12)
      - Judicial Charter (Box 12)
      - Board of JA Training, 2007 Jan 11 (Box 12)
        This was the first time the Board of Judicial Affairs invited Baran to give a training on why the Judicial Charter might need to be changed; particularly the concept of changing the standard of proof.
      - Campus Institute-Amy, 2011 (Box 12)
        Amy, CRAA Program Director, attended.
      - Sanctions/Judicial Affairs (Box 12)
        SVAW recommendations to the board on Judicial Affairs regarding Judicial Sanctions. Includes handwritten notes on Allen Berkowitz manuscript on guidelines for sanctioning perpetrators.
      - Standard of Proof (Box 12)
        Some documents related to why the standard of proof needs to change at Stanford. Includes a 2011 backlash article.
      - Op-Ed (Box 12)
        Written by two backlash attorneys who graduated from Stanford who took training materials out of context.
      - Training Justification (Box 12)
        These are the documents prepared by Baran and Amy (program director and an attorney) that outlined the justification of the training which was based on OVW standards and requirements, NCHERM standards, etc. This was necessary after Stanford's legal office decided that the best way to deal with potential backlash or threats of lawsuits by charged perpetrators was to eliminate relationship abuse from the training altogether, a very short-sighted suggestion.
      - JA Training Review/Op-Ed (Box 12)
        This was the meeting to review the JA training because of the op-ed.
  - Counseling and Psychological Services at Vaden Health Center (CAPS), Series 25
    This was an 8-hour training for CAPS staff.
    - CAPS, 2008 Apr 4 (Box 12)
      Includes handwritten notes.
    - CAPS Prep, 2008 Apr 3 (Box 12)
    - CAPS Handouts, 2008 Apr 3 (Box 12)
    - CAPS: Nature Dynamics of Relationship Abuse, 2008 Apr4 (Box 12)
  - Stanford Law Enforcement Training, Series 26
    A 2-hour training brief was delivered to Stanford PD in Stanford, CA.
    - Intimate Partner Violence on College Campuses: The Law Enforcement Response Handout Packet, 2008 May 19, 2008 May 29 (Box 12)
      This was a 16-hour training provided to Stanford Law Enforcement; co-trainer was Captain Alana Forrest (Los Gatos PD) with guest speaker Santa Clara DA Dan Nishigaya.
    - Slides Agenda (Box 12)
    - Stanford Public Safety Handouts (Box 12)
    - Public Safety Training Prep (Box 12)
    - Case Scenarios (Box 12)
    - Stanford PD Protocols (Box 12)
  - Stanford Protocols, Series 27
    The Center (Baran) developed protocols for each department in Stanford in conjunction with the Sexual Violence Advisory Board.
    Additional protocols/guidelines can be found in the electronic records series.
    - SVAB Protocol Meeting (Box 12)
    - RD Final Protocol (Box 12)
    - CAPS Guidelines (Box 12)
    - Guidelines to Respond: Appendix (Box 12)
    - Guidelines to Respond: Community Centers (Box 12)
    - SA Protocol/Procedure Research (Box 12)
    - Model Domestic Violence Workplace Policy (Box 12)
  - Center Training Folder Packets, Series 28
    These are extra training packets that were stored together.
    - Nature Dynamics of Relationship Abuse: Student Training Seminar, 2011 Apr 23 (Box 20)
    - Relationship Abuse Sexual Violence: Judicial Panelist Training (Box 20)
    - [unmarked glossy purple folder] WCC Workshop (Box 20)
    - Nature Dynamics of Relationship Abuse: Counseling and Psychological Services, 2008 Apr 4 (Box 20)
    - Nature Dynamics of Relationship Abuse: Student Training Seminar, 2010 Jan 23 (Box 20)
    - Awareness to Action Workshop: Ending Violence Against Women FEMST 100, 2013 May 18 (Box 20)
    - Colleague to Colleague: When Relationship Abuse Affects Our Coworkers, 2007 Jun (Box 20)
    - Young Women's Leadership Retreat (Trainer), 2012 May 19-20 (Box 20)
    - Young Women's Leadership Retreat (Participant), 2012 May 19-20 (Box 20)
    - Domestic Violence Training for Legal Professionals (Box 20)
    - [unmarked purple folder]: SF Bar Association: Domestic Violence Issues in Family Law Cases (Box 20)
  - Committees, Memberships, Certifications, and Conferences and Trainings Nicole Baran Attended, Series 29
    - Volunteer Work
      - [unmarked yellow folder] - Cooperative Restraining Order Clinic (CROC) Volunteer Training, 2006 (Box 22)
        Baran was a volunteer here.
    - Training
      - The Masterful Trainer: Principles, Strategies and Tools (Box 22)
      - Interpreting Seminar St. Louis, 2002 (Box 22)
      - Santa Clara Teacher Curriculum Training 2006 (Box 22)
    - Conferences attended by Baran
      See Box 28 for Conferences where Baran presented.
      - LINKS: Rhetorics, Feminisms, Global Communities, 2013 Sep 25-28 (Box 22)
      - Many Hands - One Movement: California Partnership to End Domestic Violence Annual Meeting, 2006 Sep 14-15 (Box 22)
      - Futures Without Violence: The Y Factor: Men Leading by Example, 2012 Apr 12 (Box 22)
      - Campus Training Technical Assistance Institute: Office on Violence Against Women and CALCASA, 2007 Jan 24-25 (Box 22)
      - Campus Training Technical Assistance Institute: Celebrating Our Success: Strengthening Campus Coordinated Community Response to Violence Against Women, 2010 Jun 16-17 (Box 22)
      - Ending Domestic Violence and Human Trafficking in the 21st Century, 2006 Feb 13 (Box 22)
        This was the first Domestic Violence conference that Baran's father, Nicholas Baran, attended with her.
      - Campus Training and Technical Assistance Institute, 2009 Winter (Box 22)
      - Jeanne Clery Act Training (Box 22)
      - Santa Clara Conference, 2005 (Box 22)
    - Membership Certifications
      - QPR - Vaden Mental Health, 2008 Mar 21 (Box 22)
      - Certifications (Box 22)
      - Certificates (Box 22)
      - California Partnership to End Domestic Violence Certificate for Nicole Baran, 2012 (Box 22)
      - California Partnership to End Domestic Violence Certificate for Nicole Baran, 2010 (Box 22)
      - California Partnership to End Domestic Violence, 2011 (Box 22)
      - NCADV: Membership Packet (Box 22)
    - Committees
      - Justice Courage Project Retreat, 2005 Sep 14 (Box 22)
      - 2007 National Conference on Health and Domestic Violence (AVA and FVPF) (Box 22)
      - California Partnership to End Domestic Violence: Public Policy Research Committee (PPRC) (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Global Fund for Women Gala, 2013 (Box 22)
  - TC-TAT Training/FFV Disability Workshop, Series 30
    Baran attended this Train the Trainer Workshop to integrate a response to women with disabilities into organizations and trainings. She attended the training and presented at future trainings.
    - Disability Training/TC-TAT
      - TC-TAT Contract (Box 3)
      - FFV Disability Workshop (Box 3)
      - Sample FFV Workshop Participant Information Packet (Box 3)
      - Freedom from Violence Training of Trainers, 2006 Jul 17 (Box 3)
      - [unmarked purple folder] (Box 3)
      - [unmarked purple folder] (Box 3)
      - [unmarked blue folder] (Box 3)
    - Resource Book and Trainer's Guides
      - Freedom From Violence: Preventing Violence Against Women with Disabilities: Resource Book (Box 3)
      - Freedom From Violence: Preventing Violence Against Women with Disabilities: Trainer's Guide (Box 3)
  - Board Documents and Minutes, Series 31
    Materials in this series are restricted until 2066.
    See Box 16 for Board Orientation Manual.
    - Google Analytics (Box 30)
    - Original Proposal Drafts/Copies (Box 30)
    - DVC Santa Clara MOU (Box 30)
    - Board Liaison (Box 30)
      Includes the Board Liaison How-To.
    - Board Meeting Prep (Box 30)
    - Minutes (Box 30)
    - CRAA Board of Directors - Nicole: FY0506-FY0708 (Minutes) (Box 30)
    - CRAA Board of Directors - Nicole: FY0809 onward (Minutes) (Box 30)
    - CRAA Board of Directors - Nicole: FY12-13 onward (Minutes) (Box 30)
    - Misc. Board Docs (Box 30)
  - Fundraising, Series 32
    - Fundraising
      - Blank Donation Forms (Box 17)
      - Facebook Causes (Box 17)
      - Program Update, 2007 (Box 17)
      - Publicity (Box 17)
      - Marketing Ideas (Box 17)
      - Fundraising - Jeff Chow (Box 17)
      - Corporate Fundraising (Box 17)
      - Form 990 FAQs (Box 17)
      - TEN Campaign Final Mailings (Box 17)
      - Fundraising Mailings (Box 17)
      - Fundraising Campaign Ideas (Box 17)
      - Other Nonprofits' Fundraising (Box 17)
      - Corporate Sponsorship: ROW (Box 17)
      - Fundraising Resources (Box 17)
      - Annual Fundraising Projects (Box 17)
      - Tonic Fundraiser Materials, 2012 Jun 15 (Box 17)
      - Baking for Good (Box 17)
      - Thank You Notes/Letters (Box 17)
      - Dating Violence Awareness Day (Box 17)
      - Unused Order Forms (Box 17)
      - Fundraising Ideas (Box 17)
      - Grant Writing (Box 17)
      - Grant - Good Language to Use (Box 17)
      - Fundraising (Box 17)
      - PCF Fundraising Materials (Box 17)
      - Fundraiser Plans/Info (Box 17)
    - Ten Campaign
      - TEN Campaign (Box 17)
      - Campaign Letter Drafts (Box 17)
      - TEN Campaign (Box 17)
      - TEN Flyers (Box 17)
    - Ten Party
      - Blank Raffle Tickets (Box 17)
      - TEN Auction/Raffle Materials (Box 17)
      - TEN Volunteer Materials (Box 17)
      - Accompanying Letters: Auction/Raffle (Box 17)
      - Auction Documents (Box 17)
      - TEN Flyers (Box 17)
    - Verizon Grant
      - Verizon, 2010-2011 (Box 17)
      - Verizon (Box 17)
      - Verizon, 2011-2012 (Box 17)
    - Grants/Grant Writing
      - Eileen Fisher (Box 17)
      - Gordon and Better Moore Foundation, 2012 (Box 17)
      - MOUs (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous, Series 33
    - Handwritten Notes, To Dos, Calendars
      - Priority - To Do Now (Box 19)
      - Current To Do List (Box 19)
      - To Do Lists Ideas (Box 19)
        2006-2010 To do lists include detailed to do lists for each project, OVW grant, Org goals, interns, notes, etc.
      - Calendars (Box 19)
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 19)
        Development of non-profit notes.
      - First Notes, 2005 (Box 19)
      - Notes to type (Box 19)
      - Notes to type (Box 19)
      - Nicole Notes (Box 19)
      - Typed Notes (Box 19)
      - Nicole to Read (Box 19)
      - To read (Box 19)
    - Ephemera
      - CRAA Newspaper Articles (Box 19)
      - Brochure Drafts (Box 19)
      - Center Brochures (Box 19)
      - HPS Meetings (Box 19)
      - SVAB Survey Draft, 2009 (Box 19)
      - To File (Box 19)
      - Request for Time Off (Box 19)
      - Time Sheet Template (Box 19)
      - Personnel Policies (Box 19)
      - Philosophy Project (Box 19)
    - Meetings
      - Staff Meeting Testimonials (Box 19)
      - CRAA Staff Meeting (Box 19)
    - Stanford Meetings
      - Women's Community Center (Box 19)
        Initial proposal to Women's Communty Center about the Center for Relationship Abuse Awareness.
      - Haas Center (Box 19)
      - Stanford Domestic Violence Mtg Notes (Box 19)
        Brainstorming responses to Domestic Violence in the graduate community.
      - JA Meeting (Box 19)
      - FMAV Meeting (Box 19)
        Fraternity Men Against Violence meeting.
      - Alternative to OVW grant (Box 19)
      - I-Center Mtg (Box 19)
      - SVAB Mtg, 2010 May 25 (Box 19)
      - Green at Vaden Retreat (Box 19)
    - Organization Development
      - CEU Application (Box 19)
  - Pre-MSW Job that Led to Interest in Domestic Violence, Series 34
    Baran learned that roughly 50% of her female students had been victims of dating violence, yet no workshops for boys on how to respect girls. This led to interest in teen dating violence for MSW.
    See Box 16 for Maestro Market interview in Memorabilia Binder.
    - A Voice of Her Own
      This was Baran's first job post MA in English at Stanford. It was to teach Literature and Theatre to girls from East Pala Alto in Castilleja's summer program "A Voice of Her Own."
      - A Voice of Her Own Anthology (Box 11)
        Baran designed this as a student thank you to highlight their work. Baran used this at BATV as well.
      - Teaching Possibilities - Curriculum Ideas (Box 11)
    - Bay Area Teen Voices
      Baran developed curriculum for an all-girls alternative high school program to teach girls about issues such as dating violence, rape and sex education through the medium of writing and journalism. BATV published their work in a teen magazine called "Teen Voices."
      - Nicole Keeps/Memorabilia (Box 11)
      - Employee Business (Box 11)
      - Nicole BATV Goals (Box 11)
      - Bay Area Teen Voices (Box 11)
      - Final Student Anthology (Box 11)
      - Teen Voices Mag w/ Our Feature (Box 11)
        The students were responsible for designing the feature with art and writing.
    - Curriculum and Topics
      Used in Voice of Her Own and BATV. Could be useful for middle school/high school teachers.
      - Poems (Box 11)
      - Voice (Box 11)
      - Film Study Guides (Box 11)
      - General Exercises (Box 11)
      - Sample (Box 11)
      - Body Image (Box 11)
      - Teen Pregnancy (Box 11)
      - HIV STDs (Box 11)
  - Other Jobs, Series 35
    - Support Network for Battered Women (SNBW)
      Baran's first job after MSW was Grant and Contract Manager at SNBW - she raised money and provided training for Greenbook.
      - SNBW Job App/Interview (Box 13)
      - Support Network Job – Nicole (Box 13)
      - Management Team Meetings (Box 13)
      - Support Network Volunteer Manual (Box 13)
        Baran was a hotline volunteer as well.
    - Conferences/Trainings Attended at SNBW
      - NCADV (Box 13)
      - Kaiser Training (Box 13)
        Baran presented.
      - Santa Clara Domestic Violence Conference, 2004 (Box 13)
    - Civil Domestic Violence Forms Course Manual – Judicial Counsel of California
      - Civil Domestic Violence Forms Course Manual (Box 13)
    - Amnesty International Stop Violence against Women Campaign Coordinator
      Baran was a volunteer for 1.5 years in SF, providing presentations on International VAW and was a volunteer in Paris for 2 months translating docs.
      - AI SVAW Coordinator (Job Announcement) (Box 13)
      - Domestic Violence Book Project (Box 13)
      - SVAW Coordinator Action Kit (Box 13)
      - [unmarked purple folder] SVAW Coordinator documents (Box 13)
      - Notes, Emails SVAW (Box 13)
      - Campaigning Kits (Box 13)
      - Coordinator/Training/ Guidelines Workshop Stuff (Box 13)
      - Handouts/Fact Sheets/Info Sheets (Box 13)
      - PowerPoint – Amnesty (Box 13)
    - Interim Santa Clara Domestic Violence Advocacy Consortium Director
      - Consortium Job (Box 13)
      - Family Court Collaboration (Box 13)
  - MSW (Domestic Violence Related), 2002-2003; Series 36